intheholegolf.com 2009-06-28

# Privacy Policy: InTheHoleGolf.com

**_Privacy Policy_**

IN THE HOLE! Golf is dedicated to keeping your personal information confidential. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand what information we gather and how we use it. By visiting intheholegolf.com, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.   

**Information We Collect**   

At IN THE HOLE! Golf, we respect the privacy of our customers. We collect only the information that is necessary to process your order and notify you of any changes to your order. Your information is **_never_** shared, sold, rented, leased or given to any third parties.   

**Email Addresses**  

We collect your email address during the order so that we can send you an order confirmation. We will also email you any changes to your order that may effect timing or availability of items. Once again, we **_never_** share, sell, rent, lease or give this information to any third parties.   

**Cookies**   

We do capture cookies in order for us to keep track of the items you place in your shopping cart. The "cookie" does not tell us who you are, or any other personal information about you. It only allows us to keep track of items in your shopping cart.   

**Security**   

We strive to ensure that shopping online at intheholegolf.com is more secure than using your credit card at a local retailer. IN THE HOLE! Golf uses 128 Bit Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal information, before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. Because we use SSL, placing an order online is just as safe as giving your credit card number over the telephone. Consumer protection laws protect you against any unauthorized use of your credit card. Federal law dictates that your legal liability is limited to $50 if your credit card number is used without your permission. If you suspect any illegal use of your card, call your issuing bank immediately to make sure your rights are protected.   

**External Links**  

This site contains links to other sites and other sites may be linked to this site. intheholegolf.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.   

If you have any questions regarding any of the elements of our privacy policy, please call the customer service phone number below, or e-mail us at [customerservice@intheholegolf.com](mailto:customerservice@intheholegolf.com).   

**IN THE HOLE! Golf, Inc.**  
P.O. Box 11471  
Jackson, WY 83002  
888-733-8383

InTheHoleGolf.com is your #1 resource for [ golf equipment](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-equipment/golf-equipment-1.shtml "Golf Equipment"), [ golf clubs](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-clubs/golf-clubs-1.shtml "Golf Clubs"), and [ golf training aids](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-training-aids/golf-training-aids-1.shtml "Golf Training Aids"). See our huge selection of [ golf carts](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-carts/golf-carts-1.shtml "Golf Carts"), golf balls, [ golf drivers](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-drivers/golf-drivers.shtml "Golf Drivers"), [ golf gifts](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-gifts/golf-gifts-1.shtml "Golf Gifts"), [ golf shoes](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-shoes/golf-shoes.shtml "Golf Shoes"), golf irons, golf accessories, [ golf bags](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-bags/golf-bags-1.shtml "Golf Bags"), [ golf putters,](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-putters/golf-putters-1.shtml "Golf Putters") golf wedges, hybrid golf clubs, golf apparel, ladies golf equipment, and [ golf tips](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-tips/golf-tips.shtml "Golf Tips"). If you searched for [ discount golf,](http://www.intheholegolf.com/discount-golf/discount-golf.shtml "Discount Golf") [ golf swing](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-swing/golf-swing.shtml "Golf Swing") , golf fitness, or junior golf, you're on the right site. We have the perfect golf club head cover, golf swing video, golf GPS, [ golf instruction](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-instruction/golf-instruction.shtml "Golf Instruction") , golf tee, golf simulator, [ golf store](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-store/golf-store.shtml "Golf Store") , golf shop, and most products that are golf related. We carry over 100 brands including Ogio, [ Tour Edge,](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-brands/tour-edge.shtml "Tour Edge Golf") [ Bag Boy,](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-brands/bag-boy.shtml "Bag Boy Golf") [ SkyGolf GPS,](http://www.intheholegolf.com/skygolf-gps/skygolf-gps.shtml "SkyGolf GPS") [ Sun Mountain Golf](http://www.intheholegolf.com/golf-brands/sun-mountain-golf.shtml "Sun Mountain Golf") and Tour Links. 

|  | 

|   
---  
| 

Price: $ **349.95**  
---  

Price: $ **199.95**  

Price: $ **4.95**  

Price: $ **179.95**  

Price: $ **289.95**  

Price: $ **299.95**  

Price: $ **249.95**  

Price: $ **89.95**  

Price: $ **299.95**  

Price: $ **149.95**  

Price: $ **149.95**  

Price: $ **84.95**
